(this.webpackJsonpmotto=this.webpackJsonpmotto||[]).push([[168],{302:function(e,o,t){"use strict";t.r(o),t.d(o,"general",(function(){return n})),t.d(o,"bookSession",(function(){return s})),t.d(o,"socialSession",(function(){return a})),t.d(o,"billing",(function(){return i})),t.d(o,"locations",(function(){return r})),t.d(o,"manageSession",(function(){return l}));var n=[{question:"Why should I use a personal trainer?",answer:"Personal trainers are the best way to help you reach your fitness goals more efficiently and optimally than any other fitness solution. They are uniquely qualified to tailor workout routines to fit your individual needs, help you break through plateaus, prevent injuries, and challenge your muscles in new ways. Working with a personal trainer can increase your strength, cardiovascular fitness and lean body mass more effectively than working out alone. Outside of just the physical component, most are qualified to keep you motivated mentally & emotionally. We guarantee you\u2019ll feel better in both mind & body!"},{question:"Do I have to belong to the gym in order to book a session?",answer:"No! Motto personal training is facilitated through 3 different scenarios: 1.) Your location 2.) Outdoors or a neutral location 3.) Trainer\u2019s facility. If you book a session with a trainer at their facility, all costs of using the facility are already included in the rate."},{question:"How do I know my trainer will be good?",answer:"All trainers on Motto have been carefully hand-selected and vetted by our team. While they represent a diverse selection of specialties, facility types, locations, genders and training styles, rest assured that you will be happy with whichever trainer you choose. You may see every trainer\u2019s certifications listed out on their profile. Be sure to read their bios on other unique offerings they have! We take pride knowing that most of our trainers are constantly improving their own education in order to stay the best of the best.\n \n            We offer a Money Back Guarantee. We're so confident that you'll love working out with Motto trainers, that we'll refund you the full price of your session if you're unsatisfied for any reason."},{question:"Do you offer complimentary sessions or consultations?",answer:"All our trainers have a level of quality that gives us high confidence that you will be fully satisfied with your session. The trainer you book will methodically assess your needs and goals prior to your first session through our messaging feature, and as the session progresses."},{question:"If I don\u2019t speak to anybody before I book, how do I know that the trainer will be prepared for my session?",answer:"After booking your session, you will be connected to your trainer through Motto\u2019s messaging system integrated within the platform. Your trainer will reach out to you to ensure they are fully prepared for your session. Likewise, you will be able to ask them any questions you have, or to share/confirm details your trainer may need to know. If you\u2019re unhappy with your trainer selection for any reason, you\u2019ll have until 24 hours before your session to cancel & book another."},{question:"How much do trainers cost?",answer:"Our trainers set their own rates on Motto. Their rates vary on the number of people that are in the session as well as the location you prefer. You can get discounts on sessions by booking a social session or packages."},{question:"How long do sessions last?",answer:"All sessions are 60 minutes."},{question:"Should I tip?",answer:"No. It is not customary or expected for you to tip your trainer."}],s=[{question:"How do I find a trainer in my city?",answer:"Input your location and preferences into the search bar on our home page and you will be directed to available trainers to choose from."},{question:"I am located in a different city. Can I still use Motto?",answer:"Yes! You can book trainers virtually from anywhere. You just need to choose an open time based on your time zone. For in person sessions, we will be adding markets in the future and will announce those as they are launched."},{question:"How do I contact a trainer?",answer:"Upon completion of booking a session, you will be placed into a chat with your trainer through the Motto messaging service."},{question:"Can I buy packages to save money?",answer:"Yes for 1 on 1 sessions, you can purchase 3 or 10 session packages."}],a=[{question:"What is a Social Session?",answer:"Social sessions are personal training sessions where you can add between 1-3 friends to the workout. Your trainer will still give you all personalized attention while reducing the price per person and creating a fun social experience."},{question:"How do I add friends to a Social Session?",answer:"split the cost amongst your friends. Pricing will be updated per person once your friends accept the session and you can cancel up to 24 hours in advance with no penalty."},{question:"What is a Motto class?",answer:"You can create a large format group instruction type class of your very own for you and your friends. You can set it up with your choosings of trainer, location, date and time."},{question:"How do I add friends to a class?",answer:"Once you choose the class option and complete your booking you can enter the friends you want to invite through Motto, and we will send out the invitations on your behalf. They can then accept the invitation and become part of the class. You can always invite and add friends anytime before the session from your dashboard. You\u2019ll have the option to pay for the whole session yourself or split the cost amongst your friends. Once the session is done the charge gets split evenly between all participants, unless you specified at booking that you will be paying for the whole class."}],i=[{question:"Will credit card information be stored?",answer:"You can choose to save your credit card information to be used for future sessions to make check-out even easier."},{question:"When will I be charged?",answer:"Upon booking a session, there will be a card validation however no charge will go through until completion of the session."},{question:"How do packages work and are they transferable between trainers?",answer:"Packages booked with trainers are non-transferrable to other trainers. You will be charged for the package at the time of booking and will receive credits to be used for that trainer for the allotted number of sessions."},{question:"How do payments for Social Sessions and classes get split?",answer:"For Social Sessions, trainers will have a set rate for a total 2, 3, or 4 participants in the session. The payment for the session will be split equally depending on how many people participate upon completion of the session, unless you opt to pay for the whole social session yourself.\n\n            For classes, the trainers will set a flat rate for 5-15 participants and this rate will be charged equally among those that participate, unless you opt to pay for the whole class yourself.\n            "}],r=[{question:"What locations can I get trained at?",answer:"Each trainer chooses which of the following location types they can train at: the trainer\u2019s facility, your location and/or a common outdoor location. On the trainers homepage and during the booking process you will be able to see which of these locations they offer. As you complete your booking you will be able to choose which location you prefer for your session."},{question:"How do I know details about the trainers facility?",answer:"If a trainer offers training at their facility, it is guaranteed to be in your chosen market location. Trainers that offer their facility will also have the location details listed on their profile."},{question:"If I book a session at My Location, how does the trainer know where to come?",answer:"After completion of booking, you should provide this information to the trainer in the message box that will be generated between you two."},{question:"Is pricing different for each location?",answer:"Trainers can set differential pricing for locations to account for factors such as travel and incurring gym fees."},{question:"What about the equipment?",answer:"In the case of a booking at a trainers facility or common outdoor location, the trainer will be in touch shortly after the booking with some questions so that they can prepare for the session. During this time you will be able to go over the equipment details. If you book a session at your place, the trainer will message you after the booking to assess what equipment you have and can be brought by the trainer."}],l=[{question:"What about the equipment?",answer:"You can cancel a session for no charge 24 hours prior to the start of the session."},{question:"What if I need to reschedule a session?",answer:"You cancel for no charge and rebook to new time any time prior to 24 hrs before the start of the session. If you need to reschedule and are within the 24-hour cancellation policy, you should either message your trainer directly and see if they\u2019ll accomodate a new time for you."},{question:"What happens to Social Sessions and Classes if I cancel?",answer:"If you are the person who initially booked the session, the whole session or class will be cancelled for all participants. If they would still like to have the session without you, they will need to rebook the trainer for that time slot. \n            What if I want to add more friends to a Social Session or Class after I have finished a booking?\n            "},{question:"What if I want to add more friends to a Social Session or Class after booking?",answer:"Anytime before the start of a session or class you can go to your Motto dashboard and add friends as long as it is not at full capacity."},{question:"What if I don\u2019t cancel or reschedule within 24 hours or what if I\u2019m a no-show?",answer:"The 24-hour notice requirement exists to provide trainers sufficient opportunity to fill your slot. As a matter of fairness, you will be charged for the full session if you no-show or don\u2019t cancel/reschedule prior to 24-hours before the session. "}]}}]);